ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- AFGWU Local no.1000 Agreements, 1971-1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- AFGWU Local no.1000 Agreements, 1981-1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- GPP&AWIU Local no.77 Union Shop Agreement, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Employment Policy Foundation, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Allied Research Association Annual Report, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Niagara County, New York, Market Facts, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Strategy for Success, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Teaming for Excellence Handbook (Box 9, Folder 2)
- UAW-DaimlerChrysler NewsGram for Hourly Workers, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Employers' Organization of the Metal Trades in Europe Business Study Tour to the USA, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Kort Om Svensk, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  English and Swedish
- Engineering Employers' Federation (EEF) (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Federation of Norwegian Manufacturing Industries (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Association FME-CWM, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Union Des Industries Metallurgiques et Minieres (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Federmeccanica: Italian Federation of Metalworking Industries (Box 9, Folder 10)
- The Metal Sector (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Austria (Box 9, Folder 12)
  German, English, and French
- ASM (Arbeitgeberverband der Schweizer Maschinenindustrie Jahresbericht, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  German and English
- Federation of the Metal and Electrical Industry Employers' Associations, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Arbeitgeberverband Gesamtmetall
- New Attitudes, New Opportunities, New York, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- TCIE: The Center for Industrial Effectiveness (Box 9, Folder 16)
- WNY AFL-CIO Economic Development Group, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Ergonomic Program Management Guidelines for Meatpacking Plants, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- OSHA Publications and Audiovisual Programs, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- OSHA Pamphlets, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- OSHA Pamphlets, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- 75 Ways to Improve Your Facility's IAQ, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- You're Wanted In Wyoming County (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Clearwaters, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Operations Forum, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- NAFE's Guide to a Winning Resume, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- The Parameter, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- The Environmental Illness Network, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Your Job and Childbearing, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Fatal Unintentional Farm Injuries Among Persons Less than 20 Years of Age in the United States, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Injuries Among Youth on Farms in the United States, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Lifting and Rigging Safety, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Rescue From Heights, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Wind Turbine Development: Location of Manufacturing Activity, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Building Air Quality, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Negotiating Contract Language on Health and Safety, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Workers At Risk, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Carbon Dioxide Capture and Storage, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Tackling Climate Change in the US, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- A Union Critique of Behavior-Based Safety, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- IAM Guide for Health and Safety Committees (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Energy Activity Book (Box 9, Folder 42)
- The TYTA Model: Implement for Evaluating the Company's Working Environment Costs, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- The Economic Viewpoint in Occupational Safety and Health Supervision, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- The Economics of Safety, Health, and Well-Being at Work: An Overview, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- UAW-GM Leaflets (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Priorities for Occupational Safety and Health Research in the EU-25, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- A Systematic Review of the Prevention Incentives of Insurance and Regulatory Mechanisms for Occupational Health and Safety, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Workplace Privacy, Testing for Exposure to Chemicals and Biohazards, and Issues for Labor, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- The Complete Guide to Ventilation and Indoor Air Quality Control, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  Excerpt
- Selling Safe, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Using Gardner's Theory of Multiple Intelligences t Improve Communication, Teaching, and Learning, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Take the AIS Tour (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Take the AIS Tour (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Take the AIS Tour (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Take the AIS Tour (Box 13, Folder 1)
- IBEW Locals 41 and 237 / W.N.Y. Chapter, NECA (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Buffalo Means Business, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)